All releases will be done on Curse.com AND WoWInterface.com so grab it from wherever you prefer.

Main support site:
https://muffinmangames.com

Wiki/Documenation:
https://muffinmangames.fogbugz.com/default.asp?W1

Known Bugs
https://muffinmangames.fogbugz.com/default.asp?W4


*For Cooldown counts please use Omni Cooldown Count
*For skinning install the ButtonFacade/Masque addon

To Do:
 - Pets (Favourite, and All). Maybe.
 - Add Warlocks auras to debuffs for Metaform
 - MoP potions/flasks/elixirs
 
Changes:
v5.0.4.11:
	- Added:
		Brilliant Mana Gem
		Quest: Brazier Torch, Softknuckle Poker, UDED, Transporter Power Cell, Prophetic Ink, Tahret Dynasty Mallet
		Openable: Sack o' Tokens, Pouch o' Tokens
		Fun: Blingotron
		Fishing: Ancient Pandaren Fishing Charm
		Hearth: Wormhole Generator: Pandaria
		Potion: Potion of the Jade Serpent, Potion of the Mountains, Virmen's Bite, Potion of Mogu Power

v5.0.4.10:
 - Hide bars during pet battles
 - For Warlocks, Soul Link is a buff not a shield
 - Added:
		Openable: Hero's Purse
		Fishing Tool:Dragon Fishing Pole
		Quest Items: Orange Painted Turnip, Li Li's Wishing Star, Mudmug's Vial, Zul'Drak Rat

v5.0.4.09:
 - Removed Darkmoon Adventurer's Guide from Misc.Usable.Quest since it is in fact not usable (LibPeriodicTable)
 - Funnel Cakes (from darkmoon faire) show up as food, even though WoW has them misclassified
 - Healing and Mana potions
 - Sunsong Farming button on the Extras bar
 - Removed the Track button, since it hasn't done anything in a long time
 
v5.0.4.08:
 - More foods and drinks added. I'm experimenting with getting data in a way that no longer relies on LibPT.

v5.0.4.07:
 - Massive updates to/of LibPeriodicTable. A lot of missing items should now be there.

v5.0.4.06:
 - Basic MoP Food added to LibPeriodicTable
 

v5.0.4.05:
 - Shaman: Mana Tide Totem is available now
 - Hunter class bar updates
 - Warrior updates
 - Paladin updates.
 - Hunter/Paladin Aura/Aspect button is replaced with Hunter-only Aspect button
 - Added new Poison buttons on the Rogue bar
 - Priests: Removed Vampiric Embrace, added Desperate Prayer to ER
 - DeathKnights have pets
 - Fishing on the Extras bar works again
 - Basic Monk support

v5.0.4.04:
 - Try to nicely deprecate removed button classes
 
v5.0.4.03:
 - Possible fix for Shaman Water Totems not showing (I can't test it)
 - Updated trinket list with a new experimental process (hopefully it works)
 - Updated LibPeriodicTable
 - Removed LibBabbleZone-3.0 and AceDebug-2.0
 - Removed handling of Burning Crusade instance-only items
 - Removed popup dialogs when right-clicking on bars
 - You should delete the original AutoBar folder before upgrading since some files were removed
 